

KATIE FULLMER designer & developer



ABOUT

With over a decade of experience, I specialize in designing and developing custom websites and applications, utilizing a wide range of technologies while delivering custom interfaces that focus on user experience, performance, and functionality.

I have an insatiable interest in creative problem-solving and love taking on new projects that present complex, measurable data that can be iterated on long after implementation. With my knowledge in both design and development, I foster productive teams in a collaborative environment that meets the needs of creatives and developers at the same time.

Over the years, I have come to truly enjoy the process of evaluating the scope of a product and providing new business ideas, innovations, and values that meet user needs as well as business objectives. Using an agile workflow, I typically guide clients from research and planning, to conceptualizing with prototypes, and finally to testing and implementation.

I am always eager to learn new skills, and am open to new opportunities and experiences. My days are spent with thoughtful, creative, and honest people and I strive to display all of those qualities as well.



CONTACT

□ katiegfullmer@gmail.com

www.katiefullmer.com



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana

ART HISTORY MINOR / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana



- EXPERIENCE

HEALTH CONNECTIVE / JUN 2012 - PRESENT

Senior UX Designer & Front End Developer in New Orleans, LA

Provide custom web design and application development, as well as online and print advertising for clients.

BEACHVIEW ENERGY / AUG 2017 - FEB 2020

Freelance Graphic Designer in Brunswick, GA

Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and design, branding and promotional design services.

POWER SECURE, INC. / JUL 2012 - AUG 2018

Freelance Graphic Designer in Atlanta, GA

Design the company-wide, quaterly newsletter along with a monthly newsletter for the Utility Services division along with other promtional materials.

AMERICAN ALL STAR / MAY 2008 - MAY 2017

Freelance Graphic Designer in Mandeville, LA

Design all promotional media such as brochures, t-shirts, informational binders, & folders.

DIG MAGAZINE / AUG 2011 - JUN 2012

Graphic Designer in Baton Rouge, LA

Design various medias on strict deadlines such as advertisements, posters, media kits, identities, & layouts.



AFFILIATIONS

AIGA / 2011 - PRESENT Professional Association for Design

DELTA DELTA DELTA / 2009 - 2012 Order of Omega

GDSA / 2009 - 2012

LSU Graphic Design Student Association